export const data = [
    {
    id: "0",
    question: "The client arrives at the emergency room after a burn injury that occurred in the basement at home and an inhalation injury is suspected. Which of the following would the nurse anticipate as being prescribed for the client?",
    answer: "100% oxygen via a tight fitting non-rebreather face mask",
    variants: [`oxygen via nasal cannula at 10 liters per minute`, `oxygen via nasal cannula at 15 Liters per minute`, `100% oxygen via aerosol mask`,`100% oxygen via a tight fitting non-rebreather face mask`]
    },
    {
        id: "1",
        question: "After delivery a Nurse checks the height of the uterine fundus. The nurse expects that the position of the fundus would most likely be noted",
        answer: "at the level of the umbilicus",
        variants: [`to the right of the abdomen`,`at the level of the umbilicus`,`Above the level of the umbilicus`,`one fingerbreadth above the symphysis pubic`]
    },
    {
        id: "2",
        question: "A Nurse is collecting data during the admission assessment of a client who is pregnant with twins. The client also has a five year old child. The nurse would document which gravida and para status on this client?",
        answer: "Gravida II, Para I",
        variants: [`Gravida I, Para I`,`Gravida II, Para I`,` Gravida II, Para II`,`Gravida III, Para II`]

    },
    {
        id: "3",
        question: "A mother of a toddler asks a nurse when it is safe to place the care safety seat in a face forward position. Which of the following is the best nursing response?",
        answer: "When the toddler weighs 20 pounds and is 1 year old",
        variants: [`When the toddler weighs 20 pounds and is 1 year old`,`When the weight of the toddler is more than 40 pounds`,`The seat should not be placed in a face forward position unless there are safety locks in the car.`,`The seat should never be placed in a face forward position because of the risk of the child unbuckling the harness.`]
    },
    {
        id: "4",
        question: "The nurse is providing medication instructions to an older client who is taking digoxin (Lanoxin) on a daily basis. The nurse bears in mind that which age related body changes could place the client at risk for digitalis toxicity?",
        answer: "Decreased lean body mass and glomerular filtration rate",
        variants: [`Decreased cough efficiency and vital capacity`,`Decreased Salivation and gastrointestinal motility`,`Decreased muscle strength and loss of bone density`,`Decreased lean body mass and glomerular filtration rate`]
    },
    {
        id: "5",
        question: "A nurse is teaching an older client about measures to prevent constipation. Which statement, if made by the client, that further teaching about bowel elimination is necessary?",
        answer: "I need to decrease fiber in my diet.",
        variants: [`I walk 1 to 2 miles per day.`,`I need to decrease fiber in my diet.`,` I have a bowel movement every other day.`,`I drink 6 to 8 glasses of water per day`]
    },
    {
        id: "6",
        question: "A client arrives in the emergency department complaining of chest pain that began 4hrs ago. A Troponin T blood specimen is obtained, and the results indicate a level of 0.6ng/mL. The nurse interprets that this result indicates",
        answer: "A level that indicates a myocardial infarction",
        variants: [`a normal level`,`A low value that indicates possible gastritis`,`A level that indicates a myocardial infarction`,`A level that indicates the presence of possible angina`]
    },
    {
        id: "7",
        question: "A client with a seizure disorder is taking Phenytoin (Dilantin). A sample for Serum Phenytoin level is drawn, and the nurse determines that the medication therapy is effective if the laboratory result is:",
        answer: "16mcg/mL",
        variants: [`3mcg/mL`,`8mcg/mL`,`16mcg/mL`,`24mcg/mL`]
    },
    {
        id: "8",
        question: "A client arrives in the emergency department complaining of chest pain that began 4hrs ago. A Troponin T blood specimen is obtained, and the results indicate a level of 0.6ng/mL. The nurse interprets that this result indicates:",
        answer: "A level that indicates a myocardial infarction",
        variants: [`a normal level`,`A low value that indicates possible gastritis`,`A level that indicates a myocardial infarction`,` A level that indicates the presence of possible angina`]
    },
    {
        id: "9",
        question: "Colchine is prescribed for a client with a diagnosis of Gout. The nurse reviews the client’s medical history in the health record, knowing that the Medication would be contraindicated in which disorder?",
        answer: "Renal Failure",
        variants: [`Myxedema`,`Renal Failure`,`Hypothyroidism`,`Diabetes Mellitus`]
    },
    {
        id: "10",
        question: "The client who is human immunodeficiency virus seropositive has been taking Stavudine (d4t, Zerit). The nurse monitors which of the following most closely while the client is taking this medication?",
        answer: "Gait",
        variants: [`Gait`,`Appetite`,`Level of Consciousness`,`Hemoglobin and Hematocrit blood levels`]
    },{
        id: "11",
        question: "A client with depression who has attempted suicide says to the nurse, “I should have died. I’ve always been a failure. Nothing ever goes right for me.” The nurse makes which therapeutic response to the client?",
        answer: "You have been feeling like a failure for a while",
        variants: [`I don’t see you as a failure`,`You have everything to live for`,`Feeling like this is all a part of being I’ll`,`You have been feeling like a failure for a while`]
    },{
        id: "12",
        question: "A nurse is reviewing the record of a child with a diagnosis of pyloric stenosis which data would the nurse expect to note as having been documented in the child’s record?",
        answer: "projectile vomiting",
        variants: [`watery diarrhea`,`projectile vomiting`,`increased urine output`,`vomiting large amounts of bile`]
    },{
        id: "13",
        question: "A nurse reviews the record of a 3-week old infant and notes that the physician has documented a diagnosis of suspected Hirschsprung’s disease. The nurse understands that which of the following symptoms led the mother to seek healthcare for the infant?",
        answer: "Foul-smelling ribbon like steals",
        variants: [` diarrhea`,`projectile vomiting`,`the regurgitation of feedings`,`Foul-smelling ribbon like steals`]
    },
    {
        id: "14",
        question: "A Nurse is assigned to care for a client after a cesarean section. To prevent thrombophlebitis, the nurse encourages the woman to",
        answer: "ambulate frequently",
        variants: [`ambulate frequently`,`wear support stockings`,`apply warm, moist packs to the legs`,`remain on bed rest with the legs elevated`]
    },{
        id: "15",
        question: "A Nurse checks the client’s surgical incision for signs of infection. Which of the following would be indicative of a potential infection.",
        answer: "The presence of purulent drainage",
        variants:[`The presence of serous drainage`,`The presence of purulent drainage`,`A temperature of 98.8 degrees Fahrenheit (37.1degrees Celsius)`,` The client complaint of feeling cold`]
    },
    {
        id: "16",
        question: "A Nurse is caring for a postoperative client who has a drain inserted into the surgical wound. Which of the following nursing actions would be inappropriate for the care of the drain?",
        answer: "Secure the drainage by curling and folding it and taping it firmly lit the body.",
        variants:[`Check the drain for patency`,`Observe for bright, red, bloody drainage`,`Maintain Aseptic Technique when emptying`,`Secure the drainage by curling and folding it and taping it firmly lit the body.`]
    },
    {
        id: "17",
        question: "A Nurse is caring for a postoperative client who has a drain inserted into the surgical wound. Which of the following nursing actions would be inappropriate for the care of the drain?",
        answer: "Observe for bright, red, bloody drainage",
        variants: [`Check the drain for patency`,`Observe for bright, red, bloody drainage`,`Maintain Aseptic Technique when emptying`,`Secure the drainage by curling and folding it and taping it firmly lit the body.`]
    }
    ]